owdir.com 2012-05-25

# Owdir - Open Web Directory - policies

1) Privacy Policy  
The privacy of your nonpublic personal information is important to us. We use safeguards to protect your privacy and confidentiality. This Disclosure discusses information we collect and the manner in which it is used.

We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update or modify our privacy policy simply by posting such change, update or modification on the Website. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Website.

2) Security  
We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information.

3) Information Collecting  
If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the Website and read the information contained on the Web pages, we may gather certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We may automatically gather the Internet domain, IP address from which you access our Website, and the date and time you access our Website and the pages you visit.

We may collect nonpublic personal information from you when you voluntarily provide personally identifiable information to us though our Website, such as when subscribing to a newsletter or registering a member account. We limit use of such information to the purposes for which the information was provided. However, we reserve the right to use such information to contact you regarding additional services or products that you may find useful.

If you send an e-mail message that includes personally identifiable information, for example, in an e-mail message containing an inquiry, we will use that information to respond to your inquiry. Remember that e-mail is not necessarily secure against interception.

It is our policy to not sell, rent, or give away any nonpublic personal information unless required by law. WE DO NOT DISCLOSE ANY NONPUBLIC PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOU WITH ANYONE FOR ANY PURPOSE THAT IS NOT SPECIFICALLY PERMITTED BY LAW.

We may use "cookies" to improve our service to you. Cookies may help us recall a previous visit, or recall a registered user's information. If you are not comfortable with this use, you may configure your browser to be notified when cookies are to be received and to provide you with the option of refusing cookies. However, refusing cookies may limit your ability to use our Website in its entirety. Our advertisers and sponsors may use cookies as well, we do not have access to any of this information and are not responsible for it's usage.

4) Links to Other Websites  
Our Website may contain links to Websites that are provided and maintained exclusively by third parties. Websites provided and maintained by third parties are not subject to this privacy policy. Please review the privacy policies on those Websites to understand their personal information handling practices. We make no representations concerning the privacy policies of these third party Websites.

5) Questions  
If you have any questions about our policies, you may contact us by using our contact form.
